Perris, CA 92571 m: 909.213.2114 anrowhite@gmail.com linkedin.com/antwhi

### SUMMARY

A dynamic, talented, and vision-driven Electrical Engineering graduate with a background of experience in active stabilization projects with high powered rockets, engineering proposals writing, and product specialist roles. Growth-focused leader with expertise spanning electrical engineering, systems engineering, machine-learning algorithms, technology solutions, project management, business operations optimization, embedded systems development, team leadership, Python, MATLAB, Simulink, and customer service. Exceptional engineer with keen interpersonal, communications, and resource allocation expertise.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

APPLE INC. - TEMECULA, CA, NOVEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

### PRODUCT SPECIALIST, CREATIVE

- Led and mentored small groups and individuals on individual projects, identifying the needs, advising the development, and formulating the selling and construction of new products.
- Orchestrate strategy development regarding logistics, demonstration of products and peer engagement within the company.
- Discover and review new technology, presenting the technology to both managers and small groups.
- Assist with the development of new and other team members; coordinate with team to continually improve the development process to provide quick turnarounds and high quality.
- Submit weekly report to Manager that outlines all activities and meetings; develop a sales strategy and perform in-store assisted sales to drive sell-through performance.

STARBUCKS COFFEE COMPANY – UPLAND, CA, MAY 2012 – NOVEMBER 2021

#### SHIFT SUPERVISOR

- Recruited, mentored, and motivated 20 associates in all operational practices and company policies; cultivated a professional culture which prioritized company values, completing customer interactions with integrity and appreciation, and delivering a unique and personalized experience.
- Created implemented process improvements that will enhance cycle time of production and increase productivity.
- Constructed creative solutions to staffing and performance challenges; created and improved current systems and procedures to help shape an efficient working atmosphere.

# **ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING PROJECTS**

NASA + PSYCHE SENIOR CAPSTONE PROJECT, AUGUST 2021 TO PRESENT

#### **PROJECT MANAGER**

- Leveraged theories, concepts, techniques, and standard principles for system engineering; discovered and outlined system requirements, devising the specifications of sub-systems.
- Created Arduino-based system to read and store crucial data from current and voltage sensors from photovoltaic arrays; evaluated and visualized compiled data via Python and R.
- Fostered and guided productive weekly meetings with the team, directing group through technical and system-related disciples, streamlining communication procedure to secure accurate and timely project completion.

ANTHONY WHITE Page 2

ACTIVE STABILIZATION PROJECT, CAL POLY POMONA, JULY 2019 – JULY 2021

#### **GNC ENGINEER/ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

• Constructed and tested a modular, active-stabilization system for high-powered rockets; served as team's technical writer by coordinating trade studies, component rundowns, and reports.

- Tested and verified key hardware including motor controllers, potentiometers, microcontrollers, DC motors, and sensors; applied low pass filters to decrease signal noise.
- Devised and integrated Simulink, MATLAB, and Arduino code for fin deflection, error correction, and motor position control; aided with onboarding, training, and mentorship of new student engineers.

NASA Proposal Writing and Evaluation Experience, January 2020 – March 2020

#### **ELECTRICAL ENGINEER**

- Composed a comprehensive New Technology Report for NASA-identified taxonomy; drew up conceptual design of Am-241 micro-Radioisotope Power System (mRPS).
- Tracked and identified metrics and key performance parameters; conducted research historical mRPS specifications, calculating the power output of the system.

NASA MISSION CONCEPT ACADEMY, APRIL 2019 - JUNE 2019

#### PROJECT MANAGER, GNC ENGINEER

- Assembled and submitted a Project Development Report for self-propelled Saturnian rover; created high-level system specifications.
- Managed project in accordance with standards, procedures, guidelines, schedules, priorities, and systems development methodology.
- Acted as team lead for the planning, coordination, and escalation of the project; orchestrated all concepts through the full cycle, from conception to execution.

# **EDUCATION AND CREDENTIALS**

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.Sc.) IN ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING

Arizona State University, Tempe, Arizona

<u>Relevant Coursework:</u> Computer Organization/Assembly Language, Properties of Electronic Material, Digital Circuits, Analog Circuits, Analog Integrated Circuits, Signals and Systems, Digital Signal Processing, Random Signal Analysis, Feedback Systems, Computer-Controlled Systems

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Data Analytics Certification, ASU Global Tech Program, 2021

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Classroom/project experience in: MATLAB/Simulink, SPICE, Cadence, C++, Java, Python, R
- Working knowledge of: Microsoft Office Suite, Google Suite, Asana, Tableau, Slack

### Personal Interests

Data-driven applications in space technology, space electronics and robotics, guidance and control
methods, embedded systems, systems-based engineering, analog synthesizers, human-computer
interaction, hiking, rocketry, radio astronomy, computer vision, and machine-learning applications in
power electronics